<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>博客 on Cupper</title>
    <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 博客 on Cupper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Katex Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/katex-math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/katex-math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>Enable Katex in the config file by setting the katex param to true. This will import the necessary Katex CSS/JS.
Note: Use the online reference of supported TeX functions.
Some math:
$$ \varphi = \dfrac{1+\sqrt5}{2}= 1.6180339887… $$  $$ \varphi = \dfrac{1+\sqrt5}{2}= 1.6180339887… $$
More math:
$$ \varphi = 1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\cdots} } } $$  $$ \varphi = 1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\cdots} } } $$</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupper Typography</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/cupper-typography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 15:36:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/cupper-typography/</guid>
      <description>Headings # Heading 1 ## Heading 2 ### Heading 3 #### Heading 4 ##### Heading 5 ###### Heading 6  Heading 1 Heading 2 Heading 3 Heading 4 Heading 5 Heading 6 Text *This text will be italic* _This will also be italic_ **This text will be bold** __This will also be bold__ _You **can** combine them_  This text will be italic
This will also be italic
This text will be bold</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cupper Shortcodes</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/cupper-shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 23:39:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/cupper-shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>blockquote {{% blockquote author=&amp;quot;Carl Jung&amp;quot; %}} Even a happy life cannot be without a measure of darkness, and the word happy would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness. It is far better to take things as they come along with patience and equanimity. {{% /blockquote %}}   Even a happy life cannot be without a measure of darkness, and the word happy would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA Images</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/nasa-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 20:46:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/nasa-images/</guid>
      <description>The below images are from the NASA Image and Video Library &amp;ndash; indulge yourself, revel in their beauty.
 The Sun is the star at the center of the Solar System. It is a nearly perfect sphere of hot plasma, with internal convective motion that generates a magnetic field via a dynamo process. It is by far the most important source of energy for life on Earth. Credits.    The Moon is an astronomical body that orbits planet Earth and is Earth&amp;rsquo;s only permanent natural satellite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes by Carl Jung</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/quotes-by-carl-jung/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 00:29:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/quotes-by-carl-jung/</guid>
      <description>Even a happy life cannot be without a measure of darkness, and the word happy would lose its meaning if it were not balanced by sadness. It is far better to take things as they come along with patience and equanimity. &amp;mdash; Carl Jung   The least of things with a meaning is worth more in life than the greatest of things without it. &amp;mdash; Carl Jung   Who looks outside, dreams; who looks inside, awakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivc.bioinit.com/blog/bioinfo/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>